<!DOCTYPE html>
<html lang="en">
<head>
<meta charset="UTF-8">
<title>Privacy Policy</title>
<meta name="title" content="Privacy Policy">
<meta name="DC.title" lang="en" content="Privacy Policy">
<meta name="description" content="<p>Expert furnace repair services in Austin, TX. Fast, reliable heating system repairs &amp; maintenance. 24/7 emergency service. Licensed HVAC technicians. Call now!</p><p>24/7 emergency furnace repair in Austin. Fast, reliable service by certified HVAC technicians. Call now for immediate heating system repairs &amp; maintenance.</p><p>24/7 emergency furnace repair in Austin. Fast, reliable service when you need it most. Licensed technicians ready to restore your heat anytime, day or night.</p><p>Fast, reliable furnace repair in Austin. Our expert technicians provide same-day service to get your heating system running quickly. Available 24/7.</p><p>24/7 emergency furnace repair services in Austin. Fast, reliable after-hours heating system repairs when you need them most. Call our certified HVAC technicians now!</p><p>Fast furnace parts replacement in Austin. 24/7 emergency service for when your heating system fails. Professional HVAC technicians ready to help.</p><p>Regular furnace maintenance in Austin prevents costly repairs, extends equipment life &amp; ensures optimal heating. Schedule your inspection today for peace of mind.</p><p>Keep your Austin home warm &amp; efficient with professional furnace tune-ups. Our expert technicians ensure optimal performance &amp; prevent costly repairs.</p><p>Keep your Austin home comfortable with expert furnace filter replacement services. Improve air quality &amp; efficiency with our professional HVAC maintenance.</p><p>Professional furnace system inspection in Austin. Expert diagnostics to identify issues, prevent breakdowns &amp; ensure safe, efficient heating performance.</p><p>Expert furnace performance testing in Austin. Professional diagnostics &amp; efficiency checks to ensure your heating system operates at peak condition. Fast, reliable service.</p><p>Expert furnace repair in Austin. Fix common issues like no heat, strange noises, high bills &amp; faulty ignition. Fast, reliable HVAC service when you need it most.</p><p>Expert furnace repair in Austin: Fix heating element problems quickly. Professional diagnosis &amp; repair for all furnace heating element issues. Fast service!</p><p>Expert furnace repair in Austin for thermostat issues. Fast, reliable fixes for temperature control problems, error codes &amp; system malfunctions.</p><p>Expert furnace repair in Austin. Fix noisy, weak, or non-functioning blower motors. Fast diagnosis &amp; affordable solutions. Call now for same-day service.</p><p>Expert furnace repair in Austin. Fast solutions for pilot light problems. 24/7 emergency service to get your heating system running safely &amp; efficiently.</p><p>Expert furnace repair technicians in Austin providing fast, reliable heating system repairs &amp; maintenance. Available 24/7 for all furnace brands.</p><p>Expert furnace repair in Austin by licensed HVAC technicians. Fast, reliable service for all heating system issues. Available 24/7. Call now!</p><p>Get reliable furnace repair in Austin with service warranties that protect your investment. Expert HVAC repairs backed by our satisfaction guarantee.</p><p>Get instant furnace repair cost estimates in Austin. Expert HVAC technicians provide transparent pricing for all heating system repairs and maintenance.</p><p>Get expert furnace repair in Austin from certified technicians. Professional training &amp; qualifications ensure reliable heating system repairs for your home.</p>">
<meta name="robots" content="index, follow">
<meta name="googlebot" content="index, follow, max-snippet:-1, max-image-preview:large, max-video-preview:-1">
<meta name="bingbot" content="index, follow, max-snippet:-1, max-image-preview:large, max-video-preview:-1">
<link rel="canonical" href="privacy-policy.html">
<link rel="shortcut icon"  href="img/aba-heating-and-cooling.jpeg"/>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/bootstrap@4.6.1/dist/css/bootstrap.min.css">
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://fonts.googleapis.com/css?family=Work+Sans:100,200,300,400,500,600,700,800,900&amp;display=swap" as="style" onload="this.onload=null;this.rel='stylesheet'">
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/jquery@3.5.1/dist/jquery.slim.min.js"></script>
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/popper.js@1.16.1/dist/umd/popper.min.js"></script>
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/bootstrap@4.6.1/dist/js/bootstrap.bundle.min.js"></script>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/font-awesome/4.7.0/css/font-awesome.min.css">
<style type="text/css">
.btn-md{
padding: 15px 29.6px;
border-radius: 0;
}
.t32626d67f277e086282d0953ae67101e p,.t32626d67f277e086282d0953ae67101e a,.t32626d67f277e086282d0953ae67101e span,.t32626d67f277e086282d0953ae67101e label{
font-size:16px!important;
}
html{
scroll-behavior: smooth;
}
.af486829fd0ff299286181da389fb4e87 a{
font-size:16px;
}
.t32626d67f277e086282d0953ae67101e a,.af486829fd0ff299286181da389fb4e87 a{
color:#0a0a0a!important;
text-decoration: underline !important;
}
.w0cb4365f22ef34ceda5257c227364d33:hover{
box-shadow: 0 50px 50.5px -25px rgb(0 0 0 / 30%);
transform: rotate(-2deg) scale(1.03);
}
.xed0a1ecb03aafa5324572bd431027839{
background-color:#ffc107!important;
border-color:#ffc107!important;
color:#000000!important;
}
.af486829fd0ff299286181da389fb4e87 p,.af486829fd0ff299286181da389fb4e87 span,.af486829fd0ff299286181da389fb4e87 label{
font-size:16px!important;
}
*{
font-family: 'Work Sans', sans-serif;
}
footer{
background:#131313;
color:#ffffff;
}
ul{
list-style: circle;
}
footer *{
font-size:16px !important;
}
.navbar a{
font-size: 18.1px!important;
font-weight: bold;
}
.nav-item{
padding-left:8.5px;
padding-right:8.3px;
padding-top:4.5px;
padding-bottom:5.1px;
}
.nav-link{
color: #000000;

}
a{
text-decoration: none!important;
}
footer a{
color:#ffffff;
text-decoration: underline;
}
a:hover{
color:#ffffff;background:#ffc658!important;
}
</style>
</head>
<body>
<nav class="navbar navbar-expand-lg">
<a class="navbar-brand" href="index.html"  ><img alt="img/aba-heating-and-cooling.jpeg" src="img/aba-heating-and-cooling.jpeg"  width="150px" ></a>
<button class="navbar-toggler" type="button" data-toggle="collapse" data-target="#navbarSupportedContent" aria-controls="navbarSupportedContent" aria-expanded="false" aria-label="Toggle navigation">
<span class="navbar-toggler-icon"></span></button><div class="collapse navbar-collapse" id="navbarSupportedContent">
<ul class="align-items-center ml-auto navbar-nav d-flex"><li class="nav-item"><a class="f4de638e10c711c1e565beed822e602a1 nav-link" href="news.html" rel="nofollow" >News</a></li>
  
<li class="dropdown  nav-item">
<a class="nav-link dropdown-toggle f4de638e10c711c1e565beed822e602a1" href="index.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">Furnace Repair Austin</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu dropdown-menu-right" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="index.html"  >Furnace Repair Austin</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="emergency-furnace-services.html"  >Emergency Furnace Services</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="247-emergency-response.html"  >24/7 Emergency Response</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="same-day-repair-services.html"  >Same-Day Repair Services</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="after-hours-support.html"  >After-Hours Support</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="emergency-parts-replacement.html"  >Emergency Parts Replacement</a>
  
<li class="nav-item  dropdown">
<a class="f4de638e10c711c1e565beed822e602a1 nav-link dropdown-toggle" href="preventive-maintenance.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">Preventive Maintenance</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu dropdown-menu-right" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="preventive-maintenance.html"  >Preventive Maintenance</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="annual-tune-ups.html"  >Annual Tune-ups</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="filter-replacement.html"  >Filter Replacement</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="system-inspection.html"  >System Inspection</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="performance-testing.html"  >Performance Testing</a>
  
<li class="dropdown nav-item ">
<a class="nav-link f4de638e10c711c1e565beed822e602a1 dropdown-toggle" href="common-furnace-problems.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">Common Furnace Problems</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu dropdown-menu-right" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="common-furnace-problems.html"  >Common Furnace Problems</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="heating-element-issues.html"  >Heating Element Issues</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="thermostat-malfunctions.html"  >Thermostat Malfunctions</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="blower-motor-problems.html"  >Blower Motor Problems</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="pilot-light-failures.html"  >Pilot Light Failures</a>
  
<li class="nav-item dropdown ">
<a class="f4de638e10c711c1e565beed822e602a1 nav-link dropdown-toggle" href="professional-technicians.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">Professional Technicians</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu dropdown-menu-right" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="professional-technicians.html"  >Professional Technicians</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="licensed-hvac-experts.html"  >Licensed HVAC Experts</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="service-warranties.html"  >Service Warranties</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="repair-cost-estimates.html"  >Repair Cost Estimates</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="certified-training.html"  >Certified Training</a>
<li class="nav-item"><a class="f4de638e10c711c1e565beed822e602a1 nav-link" rel=nofollow href="about-us.html">About Us</a>
</li><li class="nav-item">
<a class="xed0a1ecb03aafa5324572bd431027839 btn btn-md" href="https://abaaustin.com/contact/" rel="nofollow">Contact Us</a>
</li>
</ul>
</div>
</nav>
<section class="container" style="min-height: 80vh;">
<h1>Privacy Policy for ABA Heating and Cooling </h1>
<p>At ABA Heating and Cooling  one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors.
 This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by ABA Heating and Cooling  and how we use it. You can check out our main website here: https://abaaustin.com/</p>
<p>If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.</p>
<p>This Privacy Policy only applies to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in ABA Heating and Cooling . This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website. </p>
<h2>Consent</h2>
<p>By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its terms.</p>
<h2>Information we collect</h2>
<p>The personal information that you are asked to provide, and the reasons why you are asked to provide it, will be made clear to you at the point we ask you to provide your personal information.</p>
<p>If you contact us directly, we may receive additional information about you such as your name, email address, phone number, the contents of the message and/or attachments you may send us, and any other information you may choose to provide.</p>
<p>When you register for an Account, we may ask for your contact information, including items such as name, ABA Heating and Cooling , address, email address, and telephone number.</p>
<h2>How we use your information</h2>
<p>We use the information we collect in various ways, including to:</p>
<ul>
<li>Provide, operate, and maintain our website</li>
<li>Improve, personalize, and expand our website</li>
<li>Understand and analyze how you use our website</li>
<li>Develop new products, services, features, and functionality</li>
<li>Communicate with you, either directly or through one of our partners, including for customer service, to provide you with updates and other information relating to the website, and for marketing and promotional purposes</li>
<li>Send you emails</li>
<li>Find and prevent fraud</li>
</ul>
<h2>Log Files</h2>
<p>ABA Heating and Cooling  follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services' analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.</p>
<h2>Advertising Partners Privacy Policies</h2>
<P>You may consult this list to find the Privacy Policy for each of the advertising partners of ABA Heating and Cooling .</p>
<p>Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on ABA Heating and Cooling , which are sent directly to users' browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.</p>
<p>Note that ABA Heating and Cooling  has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.</p>
<h2>Third Party Privacy Policies</h2>
<p>ABA Heating and Cooling 's Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options. </p>
<p>You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers' respective websites.</p>
<h2>CCPA Privacy Rights (Do Not Sell My Personal Information)</h2>
<p>Under the CCPA, among other rights, California consumers have the right to:</p>
<p>Request that a business that collects a consumer's personal data disclose the categories and specific pieces of personal data that a business has collected about consumers.</p>
<p>Request that a business delete any personal data about the consumer that a business has collected.</p>
<p>Request that a business that sells a consumer's personal data, not sell the consumer's personal data.</p>
<p>If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.</p>
<h2>GDPR Data Protection Rights</h2>
<p>We would like to make sure you are fully aware of all of your data protection rights. Every user is entitled to the following:</p>
<p>The right to access – You have the right to request copies of your personal data. We may charge you a small fee for this service.</p>
<p>The right to rectification – You have the right to request that we correct any information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request that we complete the information you believe is incomplete.</p>
<p>The right to erasure – You have the right to request that we erase your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to restrict processing – You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to object to processing – You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to data portability – You have the right to request that we transfer the data that we have collected to another organization, or directly to you, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.</p>
<h2>Children's Information</h2>
<p>Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.</p>
<p>ABA Heating and Cooling  does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.</p>
<h2>Publisher</h2>
<p>
This website is owned and published by:
ABA Heating and Cooling </br>
</br>
2409 Richcreek Rd #2,</br>
Austin</br>
TX</br>
https://abaaustin.com/</br>
</br>
</p>
</section>
<footer>
<div class="pt-5 py-4 container" >
<div class="row"><div class="col-lg-3">
<p>ABA Heating and Cooling </p>
<p>City : Austin</p>
<p>State : TX</p>
<p>Zip : 78757</p>
<p>Address : 2409 Richcreek Rd #2,</p>
<p><a class="f4de638e10c711c1e565beed822e602a1" href="https://www.google.com/maps/place/?cid=6115723188472229837" rel="nofollow"> Google Business Profile</a></p>
<p>Company Website : <a class="f4de638e10c711c1e565beed822e602a1" href="https://abaaustin.com/" rel="nofollow">https://abaaustin.com/</a></p>
</div><div class="col-lg-3"><p><a class="f4de638e10c711c1e565beed822e602a1" href="sitemap.html" rel="nofollow">Sitemap</a></p>
<p><a class="f4de638e10c711c1e565beed822e602a1" href="privacy-policy.html" rel="nofollow">Privacy Policy</a></p>
<p><a class="f4de638e10c711c1e565beed822e602a1" href="about-us.html" rel="nofollow">About Us</a></p>
</p>
</div></div>
</div>
</footer> 
<script type="text/javascript">
document.addEventListener('DOMContentLoaded', function() {
var dropdowns = document.querySelectorAll('.dropdown-hover');
function showDropdown() {
var dropdownMenu = this.querySelector('.dropdown-menu');
dropdownMenu.style.display = 'block';
}
function hideDropdown() {
var dropdownMenu = this.querySelector('.dropdown-menu');
dropdownMenu.style.display = 'none';
}
function handleClick(event) {
var target = event.target;
window.location.href = target.getAttribute('href');
}
dropdowns.forEach(function(dropdown) {
dropdown.addEventListener('mouseenter', showDropdown);
dropdown.addEventListener('mouseleave', hideDropdown);
var dropdownMenu = dropdown.querySelector('.dropdown-toggle');
dropdownMenu.addEventListener('click', handleClick);
});
});
</script> 
</body>
</html>
